It looks like no one in Koichi's
family knows where he went either.
And from the sound of things,
they're close to calling the police.
Dammit, so he really is missing.
Yukako is nowhere to be seen either.
I feel like it's all my fault.
Wait!
You don't think she snapped
and snuffed him out, do you?
Well, no.
I don't think it's come to that.
Regardless, she's holding him captive.
Come on, we need to
find him and do it fast.
I feel like we don't have much time
left if we want to find him alive.
It won't open!
This can't be happening to me!
Damn,
I'm pretty sure there was a
movie that has the answer I need,
but I never ended up watching it
because it looked way too long!
I think I've almost got this
ridiculous thing figured out.
One, and then four, zero, zero, open!
I washed your pajama bottoms,
as well as your underwear.
Is there a problem?
I can't help if I don't know what's wrong.
It's just that I'm a
freshman in high school.
How could I let this happen?
I'd be embarrassed if I didn't already
feel like a pathetic waste of a human.
Enough.
Please, stop this.
I mean, surely you must despise me by now.
Don't I disgust you?
Won't you please just let me go home now?
What could you possibly like about
a guy who just peed his pants?
Koichi, you poor pitiful thing. How awful.
I must be putting your gentle
heart through so much agony.
I'm such a bad girl,
the lowest of the low.
Nothing I say has any effect on her.
I think I'm gonna cry.
First I wet myself, now this.
What the hell is going on?
There's just one thing.
I was watching when you
talked about being a pathetic
human being and saw a sparkle
deep behind your eyes.
What I saw in that moment
was positively intoxicating.
If I didn't know any better, I'd swear
you were hiding an ace up your sleeve.
And if I'm being honest, it
makes me like you even more.
It's the reason I want to
learn everything about you.
After all,
what's a little bit of poop and snot when
you're madly in love with your soulmate?
Right, Ko?
I'm surprised you were worried.
Washing your soiled unmentionables filled
me with a kind of joy
that I'd never known.
Look!
What do you think?
I'm making an electric chair.
With any luck, it'll be ready
for our dinner time studies.
I was thinking about trying out
a new Italian recipe tonight.
So I have to stock up on olive oil.
I can't wait.
Somebody help me!
She's going further and
further off the deep end!
I have to get out of here faster!
She's seriously going to kill me!
But...
How exactly do I do that?
I might be completely wrong about this?
But even if someone's found
a way to keep Koichi quiet,
can he still call out
for help using Reverb?
Ideally, yes, but Reverb only
has a range of about 50 meters.
If he was taken somewhere isolated,
his powers would be no good.
It's like looking for
a needle in a haystack.
Hang on.
She said something about
stocking up on more olive oil.
But she wouldn't go shopping at this hour.
Maybe she's doing a phone order?
Hey, could it be?
It is! A payphone!
I'm 48 meters away!
Yes, it's just within range!
Thank goodness Reverb is a soundstand!
Now I can signal Josuke and get some help!
I don't have any 10 yen coins!
planes!
I was in my pajamas
when I was dragged here!
Should I just dial 110?
But if I do that, she might
kill the officers! Damn it!
I'll just have to find some
other way to contact Josuke!
You were wondering whether there was a
payphone nearby, weren't you, Koichi?
Yukako!
You don't have to pretend.
I know precisely what you're thinking.
Since I told you that I was
going to go buy some olive oil,
you thought there must
be a payphone nearby.
but it needed 10 yen coins,
which you don't have.
Does that about cover it?
Oh, there's a payphone? How about that?
Feigning ignorance?
I give up on the notion of
calling someone for help.
You're not taking a single step
outside this house until I say so.
But so you won't be tempted, I'm going
to destroy the phone's emergency button.
Would you like anything?
No, I guess not.
There's just no reasoning with her.
That was it.
My last shot at getting help.
What is this writing?
Why are there sounds coming out of my arm?
The phone's calling someone.
That doesn't make sense.
I never dialed a number.
Higashikata speaking.
I got through!
If the right signals are transmitted,
a push-button phone will connect!
Koichi!
Hey, is that you?
It's me, Josuke!
Koichi, where are you?
What's that?
I hear waves crashing.
Koichi!
Koichi?
So I was right, you do
have a power like me.
Yes, I did it!
Now Chosuke's gonna rush over
here and rescue me for sure.
It'll take 20 minutes tops by car.
I just have to figure out a way to
hold out until they can get here.
A payphone and the sound of waves.
The only place Koichi
could be is right here.
Koichi.
Koichi!
She's coming back to the house!
Looks like I have no choice but to fight!
Open this door, Koichi!
You want in so bad, why
don't you break it down?
A broken door will definitely
make Josuke stop and take notice.
You've made me very happy, Koichi.
Discovering you have
powers like I do is the
most wonderful surprise
I could have received.
Though I have to say I'm a bit
irritated that you kept this a secret.
Even so, I'm happy you're like me.
Because when a man and a woman decide to
spend the rest of their lives together,
nothing is more important than
a relationship built on love,
trust, and shared values, right?
The two of us share something no one else
could ever dream of having think about it.
We could be the perfect couple
So please Koichi open the door?
When I say open the door
open the goddamn door!
Did you actually believe
we'd be the perfect couple?
Why can't you understand how
much I hate what you're doing?
That noise will keep
bombarding you until you
renounce your love for me
and cry for forgiveness!
I hate you!
You're not making sense.
This foolishness is
practically inaudible to me.
I hate you! No!
What's going on?
This isn't at all like
what happened with Tamami.
Her delusions are too strong.
But I didn't think it'd be
completely useless on her.
I finally found the one person I'm
bound to with the red thread of fate,
and I won't let anything come between us.
Some people never find their soulmate.
Don't you understand how lucky we are?
Oh, Koichi, my plan was to turn
you into an outstanding man,
but recent events have
forced me to change my mind.
So until you fall madly in love with
me, you will remain in this house.
And make no mistake, you
are going to love me!
Or else...
I might murder you.
I can't let her in here, no matter what!
I just need to land one
more attack with Reverb!
If I go all out, I'll be able
to unleash an even louder sound.
Reverb!
Something's wrong with Reverb.
Are you all right?
He's not moving!
No, what's happening to him?
Did he collapse because he sensed
that our situation is hopeless?
You're kidding me!
REVERB IS DEAD!
What happened?
No, Reverb.
He's been turned into a
lifeless husk! But how?
A stanza manifestation of the soul!
Which means I must have
pushed mine too far past
its breaking point and
collapsed under the pressure!
Ah!
I didn't mean for this to happen, Reverb!
What?
What the hell did he call that thing?
A stand?
Whatever it is, I have to stop it!
Get this thing out of my way!
She's gonna kill me!
If that psycho makes it through the door
and catches me, I'm as good as dead!
Koichi, open this door!
I have to stop her from
getting in here somehow!
If only there was a way for
that door to blow her far away!
It broke out of its shell!
Where did you put it?
Answer the damn question, Koichi!
Where did you put that thing?
What?
Wait, is that...
I don't believe it! It's reverb!
It's still alive!
It must have been changing into a
new form while it was in that shell!
Is this a joke?
Its design hasn't really changed at
all, besides the fact that it shrunk.
Regardless, changing
shape isn't going to help.
Oh man, it's fast!
Where's this wind coming from?
Whoa!
It actually blew her away!
I don't know how, but some kind of
wind blasted her out of the house!
Damn, what just happened to me?
What did that stand do?
Is that?
Yeah, it's Reverb's writing.
I get it now.
She touched the graffiti door
and the writing became real.
The sensation of the word Fish literally
sent her flying. Wait a minute.
Right before it happened,
I wish the door would open.
blow her away.
I didn't realize it, but I was
controlling that sensation.
This is the brand
new Reverb.
Reverb Act Two!
Oh, Koichi.
It's them.
This vacation spot is the one place I know
that's by the sea and
has lots of empty houses.
Yeah, that's great and all.
But there are still tons
of houses around here.
How do we find out which one he's in?
By finding the phone booth.
Koichi did call us using
a public phone, right?
Once we find that booth, we'll start
searching the nearby houses one by one. Right.
Search around all you want, sweet,
adorable Koichi belongs to me.
I'll never let anyone else have him.
I strongly suggest you
keep your distance, Yukako.
And you should believe me when I tell you?
There's just no way that
your powers can compete.
with Rebervac 2's new abilities.
Our days of playing house are over.
Now my left eyelid is twitching.
Since I was a kid, getting upset
always set off my orbicularis oculi.
It was like a weird chick that
said I was about to get violent!
Oh, and just so you know,
one stupid little modification
doesn't suddenly make you a big shot!
I'm gonna have to get a little rough now!
Ah! Damn it!
How could you do this?
Koichi, you shit!
You earned my hand!
When you said you were
gonna get a little rough,
I didn't think you
meant your vulgar mouth.
How dare you do this after all I've done?
You piss-sweating shrimp!
You are mine!
You belong to me, yet you dare defy me!
I own you!
Reverb, act two!
I missed?
Josuke!
Yeah, I heard it.
Could be wrong, but it
sounded like something broke.
Hey, I think it's that house!
Man, I can't believe she can make
her hair grow to this length.
Her soul's more powerful than I thought.
but it's a dark and vindictive soul.
So its name is Reverb. Pathetic.
I've figured out the
secret behind your trick.
All I have to do is avoid
touching that writing.
Now I'll ask you this one more time.
You love me, right?
Koichi.
I'd advise against saying no
if you want to keep living.
I'm completely prepared to tear down
this house and bury you in the wreckage.
And if you die, you'll
be mine for all eternity.
You'll remain in my heart as a
personal memory of love everlasting.
Time to answer the question!
I have, but you refused to listen, which
is how I got wrapped up in this whole mess.
So now, for the upteenth time, I don't.
Don't make me say it again.
You're dead, Koichi!
Weren't you listening to what I said?
Now that I have this new power,
you can't hold me hostage anymore!
You're touching the writing
that's gonna blow you away!
Not bad for a pants-wetting
little shrimp, huh?
Oh no, why did her hair turn white?
She's not dead, is she?
Good, she's alive!
She might be a deranged, love-obsessed,
matted mess of a she-devil,
but I guess I should be happy.
I wasn't able to keep hold
of you with my loving heart,
but I think I'll destroy your
precious standard consolation!
You disrespecful heart-taker!
Even as beaten up as she is,
she's still able to fight?
Her will is scary and tense!
Not another word!
Intense? Screw you!
You panty-wetting douche!
How dare you even speak when
you're the one who did this to me!
You rejected my love,
blasted me with your stand, and
made my treasured hair turn white?
You pathetic little jerk-off!
I loved you with every fiber of my being,
but I refuse to let you get away
with doing this to my gorgeous hair!
I don't care if you're my soulmate.
No one gets to undermine my beauty!
I'm gonna yank off your piss-soaked prick,
rip out your insides, and feed him to you?
as you choke on my merciless love!
Please, stop this!
I told you, no words!
It's time to get what's coming to you!
What the hell was that sound just now?
Yukako, you gotta let go of my stand!
Grab ahold of something!
The cliff is about to crumble!
When Reverb was listening
for your heartbeat,
it also heard the ground
slowly splitting underneath us!
Don't try bullshitting me to save
yourself from your punishment!
I have to let go, so I can
grab onto something else! Shit!
I don't have time!
I told you the ground would crumble.
Of course, you've proven time and again
that nothing I say to you sinks in.
You mean you'd already placed it there?
So while I was in a frenzy
trying to rip Reverb to pieces,
you were using your stand to write
on that rock beneath the cliff.
The entire time I was thinking
of how to kill Koichi,
He was focusing all of his energy
on how to save me from myself.
I've lost.
He completely defeated me.
Now, if I'm being honest with myself,
I lost the moment I met Koichi.
Hey, Koichi, over here!
Are you still in one place?
You're not hurt, are you, Koichi?
Josuke and Okuyasu, you guys found me!
What took you two so long to get here?
But now, I think I'm even
more in love with him.
I don't care if he ignores
me for the rest of our lives.
Just thinking about him fills me with joy.
Koichi!
Hey, over there!
Isn't that Yukako?
Her hair has turned completely white!
Whoa, what happened?
No idea, but look!
The way she's smiling, you'd
think she was on top of the world!
And she's looking over here! What?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
That's really creepy.
Quick, let's get out of here!
Selfie Josuke!
It's every man for himself!
Well, I'll be a seagull's beak.
Did you see that?
Oh, no, Grandpa.
You're not allowed to have a drink.
Cape Bang.
After apparently witnessing a
young woman jump to her death?
Only to bounce off the rocks
below with a gentle Bang,
a pair of fishermen
created an urban legend.
and a new appellation.
Hirose, I can tell you really
gave it your all this time.
You get scores like that when you study.
Oh, man.
I'm not sure how I should feel about this.
Come stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what hit you!
When I get to you?
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
But ooh, I got to find you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
But ooh, I got to find you.